

Apostolos Gouvalas Full-stack Web Developer

Full-stack developer with over 6.7 years of experience in PHP, SQL and JavaScript, among other languages. With attention to detail and a passion for problem solving, I am willing to contribute my skills to dynamic and challenging projects.

□ apo.gouv@gmail.com

+30-697 8811 469

cubedesigns.gr

▼ Thessaloniki, Greece

SOCIAL

in linkedin.com/in/apostolos-gouvalas

github.com/ApoGouv

EDUCATION

MS in Mobile and Web Computing

2016 - 2018

[Distinction]

International Hellenic University (Thessaloniki, Greece)

Digital Systems Degree, majoring in "Communication and Network Systems"

2004 - 2013

University of Piraeus - Department of Digital Systems (Piraeus, Athens, Greece)

LANGUAGES

Greek [Native language]
English [Proficiency of Michigan & IELTS 7.5]
Spanish [A2 in progress]

SOFTWARE & TOOLS

VSCode, Git, Linux, Windows, cPanel, etc.

HOBBIES

Cycling, Dancing Salsa/ Kizomba, Sudoku, Rock Music

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Web Developer

Nov 2017 - Present | Mental Media (former MultiHosting)

- Development of ecommerce websites, with OpenCart, CS-Cart, PrestaShop, WooCommerce, etc., as well as custom functionalities and integrations with ERP programs.
- Website development (portfolios, corporate, personal, etc.) - WordPress, Joomla, etc.
- Company projects WHMCS, Laravel, vBulletin, Joomla, etc.

Front-end Web Developer

Aug 2017 - Oct 2017 | PSDGator

 Convert design mockups from PSD or AI to valid HTML and CSS or WordPress Themes.

Full-stack Web Developer

Dec 2015 - Present | Freelance

 Construction of websites, e-shops and custom solutions according to customer requirements

Front-end Web Developer

Apr 2014 - May 2014 | igraphics.gr

 Created the user interface, based on the supplied graphic mockups, for applications to visualize the results of the 2014 Italian European Parliament Elections and display past Italian election results, with valid HTML, CSS and jQuery.

CERTIFICATES

JavaScript, React, Node.js, PHP, κ.α.

2017 - 2024 | Udemy

JavaScript Essentials

Build a Social Network from Scratch:
JavaScript PHP + MySQL

The Complete Node.js Developer
Course (2nd Edition)

Oct 09, 2017

The Complete JavaScript Course:
Build a Real-World Project

Sep 11, 2017

Aug 14, 2017